SVITLANA HAVRYLIUK

21000 Vinnitsa, Ukraine | +380632811596 | svetly2011@gmail.com



Profile

I have been doing web development for over 4 years and I specialize in creating WordPress sites. I understand someone else's code, quickly master software products, technologies and languages. The ability to work with a team, an excellent solution to problems and interpersonal skills.

Technical skills

- Programming languages of HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, jQuery, Ajax, Joomla, Wordpress, Instantcms, OpenCart. Begining knowledge Reactjs, Laravel, Drupal, Sass.
- Website optimization

Work Experience

Freelance Web Developer Freelance Vinnitsa

Jul 2014 to Current

- Layout from a PSD layout to a finished web page using HTML markup tools and cascading style sheets (CSS) with JavaScript, AJAX and JSON. Using API and other widgets.
- Development of dynamic websites in accordance with customer requirements on Php, Wordpress, phpBB, Instant sms, Opencart.
- Adaptation and modification of modules and functions necessary for the tasks of the client.

Programmer Metastudio , Vinnitsa

Nov 2011 to Jul 2014

- Development of pages and navigation tools that met users' expectations for the site imarketing.com.ua on the basis of the engine for creating social networks, communities, portals InstantCMS.
- Uses programming features in JavaScript and other libraries as needed.
- Implemented Google and SEO campaigns for the site.
- Writing technical texts for filling all sections of the site.
- Improve product marketing goals by creating communication initiatives and branding strategies to expand customer reach.

Manager Firm Vincard, Vinnitsa

Jun 2010 to Okt 2011

- Management of production and sale of plastic cards in the Vinnitsa region, as well as in Ukraine and abroad.
- Search for new customers and the conclusion of the most mutually beneficial contracts.
- Thanks to effective presentations, we managed to attract more than 50 new customers.

• A greater number of negotiations were held with potential customers, most of which ended successfully.

Computer Systems Egineer Ukrtelekom, Vinnitsa

Jun 2007 to May 2009

- Diagnostics and troubleshooting related to the availability of the Internet and servers both in the centre and in remote servers in the Vinnytsia region.
- Monitoring network performance, providing statistical reports on network performance, both in real time and for past measurements.
- Network monitoring and server monitoring both on-site and off-site.
- Consultation and assistance to Internet users from Ukrtelecom.

Manager Firm Alsita, Kiev

Nov 2006 to May 2007

- Engaged in the wholesale of computer equipment and electronics.
- Daily revealed the needs of customers, negotiating by phone and in person with the first persons of small and medium-sized businesses in Ukraine.

Accountant Nov 2003 to Sep 2006 Credit Union named after Ivan Kulmatitsky, Vinnitsa

- Conducting accounting documentation, conclusion of contracts with clients.
- Managed departments of payables, receivables and settlement statements.
- Acceptance and control of primary accounting documentation
- Mapping on the accounts of accounting operations associated with the movement of fixed assets, inventory and cash.

Education

Fundamentals of Information Security Prometheus, Ukraine

2017

- The main cyber threats, who and why they create them.
- How to protect personal information from loss or theft.
- The subject of electronic finance security.

Computer System Engineer

2002

- Vinnytsia National Technical University, Vinnitsa, Ukraine
 Learning programming languages to create applications and web sites.
- Creating and configuring a computer network.

PC Accountant Operator Vinnitsa Inter-Regional Technical School 4

1994

- Possession of office software on a PC.
- Accounting operations at the enterprise.